[{"id":1,"question":"Which command adds members to the replica set from MongoDB shell?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`rs.add(\"<hostname>\")`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`replicaSetAdd(\"<hostname>\")`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`rs.insert(\"<hostname>\")`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`replica.add(\"<hostname>\")`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":2,"question":"Which MongoDB shell command should you use to back up a database?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"restore","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"backup","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"mongobackup","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"mongodump","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":3,"question":"Which shell query displays all citizens with an age greater than or equal to 21?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.citizens.select('WHERE age >= 21')`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.citizens.where('age >= 21')`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.citizens.find('WHERE age >= 21')`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.citizens.find({age: {$gte: 21}})`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":4,"question":"What does a MongoDB collection consist of?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"data","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"documents","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"fields","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"rows","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":5,"question":"Given an ObjectId in `_id`, how do you get the time it was created?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`getDateTime(_id)`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`_id.createDate()`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`_id.getTimestamp()`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`_id.getDateTime()`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":6,"question":"Given a cursor named myCursor, which command returns a boolean value?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"myCursor.hasNext()","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"myCursor.sort()","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"myCursor.next()","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"myCursor.find()","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":7,"question":"Which command returns a specific document in the user's collection?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.users.find({_id: 1})`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`db.users.seek({_id: 1})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.users.query({_id: 1})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.query.users({_id: 1})`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":8,"question":"To import a JSON array into Mongo, what flags are needed with MongoDBimport?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`--type jsonArray`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`--json`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`--type json`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`--jsonArray`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":9,"question":"Choose the shell command that connects to a MongoDB database.","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"mongo","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"mongod","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"mongoconnect","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"dbconnect","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":10,"question":"In the MongoDB shell, how can you tell if an index was used with a query?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"db.customers.find({lastName: 'smith'}).explain()","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"db.customers.find({lastName: 'smith'}).perf()","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"db.customers.find({lastName: 'smith'}).plan()","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"db.customers.find({lastName: 'smith'}).usedIndex()","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":11,"question":"Suppose your aggregation pipeline terminated with an exception referring to exceeded memory limit. What is the best way to resolve the issue?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Set useMemory to twice amount indicated in exception.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Switch a 64 bit instance of MongoDB.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Increase the memory of the MongoDB server.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Set allowDiskUse to true.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":12,"question":"What is the recommended way to delete a user?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"db.deleteUser(\"user\")","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"db.removeUser(\"user\") DEPRECATED","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"db.remove(\"user\")","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"db.dropUser(\"user\")","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":13,"question":"What the primary database in a replica set fails, when does failover begin?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"once the primary has been down for 10 minutes","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"once the primary reboots","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"immediately","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"after the administrator reboots the primary","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":14,"question":"What is the correct option to set up Kerberos when starting MongoDBd?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`--setParameter authenticationMechanisms=GSSAPI`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`--setAuthentication=GSSAPI`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`--setParam auth=K`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`--setAuth method=Kerberos`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":15,"question":"What is the purpose of an arbiter in a replica set?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"It monitors replica set and sends email in case of failure","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"It casts the tie-breaking vote in an election.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"It holds a backup copy of the database.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"It reboots the failed server.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":16,"question":"You want to know how many types of items you have in each category. Which query does this?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.product.group({_id: \"$category\", count: {$sum:1}})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.product.aggregate($sum: {_id: \"$category\", count: {$group:1}})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.product.aggregate($group: {_id: \"$category\", count: {$sum:1}})`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`db.product.aggregate($count: {_id: \"$category\", count: {$group:1}})`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":17,"question":"To restrict the number of records coming back from a query, which command should you use?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"take","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"limit","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"max","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"skip","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":18,"question":"You have a collection named restaurants with the geographical information stored in the location property, how do you create a geospatial index on it?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.restaurants.CreateIndex({location: \"2dsphere\"})`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`db.restaurants.geospatial({location: \"2dsphere\"})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.restaurants.CreateIndex(\"2dsphere\":\"location\")`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.restaurants.CreateIndex({geospatial: \"location\"})`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":19,"question":"How do you find documents with a matching item in an embedded array?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.customers.findmatch ({\"jobs\":\"secretary\"})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.find ({\"jobs:secretary\"})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.find ({\"jobs\":[\"secretary\"]})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.find ({\"jobs\":\"secretary\"})`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":20,"question":"Which query bypasses the first 5 customers and returns the next 10?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.customers.find({}, {skip: 5, limit: 10})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.find({}.page(5).take(10))`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.find({}).skip(5).take(10)`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.find({}).skip(5).limit(10)`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":21,"question":"How do you create a text index?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.customers.createIndex({firstName, lastName})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.createTextIndex({firstName, lastName})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.createIndex({firstName: \"text\", lastName: \"text\"})`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.createText({firstName: 1, lastName: 1})`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":22,"question":"Assuming you have customers collection with a firstName and lastName field, which is the correct MongoDB shell command to create an index on lastName, then firstName both ascending?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.customers.createIndex(\"lastName, firstName, ASC\")`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.addIndex({lastName:\"ASC\", firstName: \"ASC\"})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.newIndex({lastName:1, firstName:1})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.createIndex({lastName:1, firstName: 1})`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":23,"question":"One of the documents in your collection has an _id based upon an older database design and you want to change it. You write an update command to find the document and replace the _id but the _id isn't changed. How should you fix the issue?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Set the replace option to true.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Use the replaceOne() command instead.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"You can't. Once set, the _id field cannot be changed.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Use the updateOne() command instead.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":24,"question":"A compound index allows you to _ ?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Calculate interest quickly.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Accomplish nothing, since compound indexes aren't allowed in Mongo.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Use more than one field per index.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Combine fields in different collations.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":25,"question":"Why are ad-hoc queries useful?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"They do not have to use the same operators.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"You do not need to structure the database to support them.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"They autogenerate reports.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"They run faster than indexed queries.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":26,"question":"How often do the members of a replica set send heartbeats to each other?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"every 2 minutes","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"every 5 seconds","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"every 2 seconds","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"every 10 seconds","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":27,"question":"Which command returns all of the documents in the customers collection?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.customers.all();`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.find().customers();`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.find();`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.show();`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":28,"question":"Given a cursor named myCursor, pointing to the customers collection, how to you get basic info about it?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`myCursor.stats()`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`myCursor.dump()`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`myCursor.info()`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`myCursor.explain()`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":29,"question":"What is true about indexes?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"They speed up read access while slowing down writes.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"They secure the database from intruders.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"They speed up reads and writes.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"They speed up write access while slowing down reads.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":30,"question":"What is the preferred format to store geospatial data in MongoDB?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Latitude, longitude","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"XML","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"GeoJSON","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"BSON","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":31,"question":"Which programming language is used to write MongoDB queries? (_Alternative_: In the MongoDB shell, what programming language is used to make queries?)","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Python","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"JavaScript","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"SQL","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"TypeScript","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":32,"question":"You have two text fields in your document and you'd like both to be quickly searchable. What should you do?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Create a text index on each field.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"MongoDB is not able to do this.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Create a compound text index using both fields.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Create a text index on one field and a single field index on the other.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":33,"question":"To import a CSV file into MongoDB, which command should you issue?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"mongorestore","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"mongoi","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"upload","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"mongoimport","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":34,"question":"In an MongoDB mapReduce command, the reduce function should _.","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"access the database","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"be called only when the key has a single value","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"access the database only to perform read operations","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"not access the data","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":35,"question":"On a newly created collection, which field will have an index?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"the name field","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"the ObjectId field","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"the `_id` field","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"no field will have an index","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":36,"question":"You have a collection of thousands of students. You'd like to return the second set of 20 documents from the sorted collection. What is the proper order in which to apply the operations?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"limit, skip, sort","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"sort, limit, skip","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"limit, sort, skip","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"sort, skip, limit","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":37,"question":"You would like the stats() command to return kilobytes instead of bytes. Which command should you run?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.vehicle.stats(1024)`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`db.vehicle.stats(\"kilobytes\")`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.vehicle.stats(true)`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.vehicle.stats(\"kb\")`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":38,"question":"You want to modify an existing index. What is the best way to do this?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Use the `reIndex()` command to modify the index.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Delete the original index and create a new index.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Call the `createIndex()` command with the update option.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Use the `updateIndex()` command.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":39,"question":"You need to delete the index you created on the description field. Which command will accomplish this?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.vehicle.dropIndex(\"description_text\")`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`db.vehicle.dropIndex({\"description\":\"text\"})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.vehicle.removeIndex({\"description\":\"text\"})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.vehicle.removeIndex(\"description_text\")`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":40,"question":"You would like to know how many different categories you have. Which query will best get the job done?","code":"Note: count() works with find(...) but length works with distinct","reference":"Note: count() works with find(...) but length works with distinct","choices":[{"text":"`db.vehicle.distinct(\"category\")`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.vehicle.unique(\"category\")`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.vehicle.distinct(\"category\").count()`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.vehicle.distinct(\"category\").length`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":41,"question":"From the MongoDB shell, how do you create a new document in the customers collection?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.customers.add({name: \"Bob\"})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.save({name: \"Bob\"})`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.create({name: \"Bob\"})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.new({name: \"Bob\"})`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":42,"question":"Which field is required of all MongoDB documents?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`_id`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`_name`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"ObjectId","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"mongoDB is schema-less so no field is required","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":43,"question":"A MongoDB instance has at least what three files?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"data, namespace, and journal","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"namespace, journal, and log","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"journal, data, and database","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"data, log, and journal","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":44,"question":"You'd like a set of documents to be returned in last name, ascending order. Which query will accomplish this?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.persons.find().sort({lastName: -1}}`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.persons.find().sort({lastName: 1}}`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`db.persons.find().sort({lastName: ascending}}`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.persons.find().sort({lastName: $asc}}`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":45,"question":"What is NOT a standard role in MongoDB?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"restore","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"read/write","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"dbadmin","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"delete collections","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":46,"question":"Which MongoDB shell command deletes a single document?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.customers.delete({_id: 1});`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.drop({_id: 1});`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.drop.customers({_id: 1});`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.remove({_id: 1});`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":47,"question":"Using the MongoDB shell, how do you remove the customer collection and its indexes?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.customers.remove({}).indexes();`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.remove({});`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.drop();`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.delete();`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":48,"question":"By default, applications direct their read operations to which member of the replica set?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"primary","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"arbiter","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"secondary","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"backup","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":49,"question":"You need to get the names of all the indexes on your current collection. What is the best way to accomplish this?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.people.getName();`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.people.reIndex({names: 1});`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.people.getIndexKeys();`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.people.getIndexes();`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":50,"question":"You are going to do a series of updates to multiple records. You find setting the multi option of the update() command too tiresome. What should you do instead?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Use the replaceMany() command instead","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Use the updateMulti() command instead","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Use the updateMany() command instead","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Set the global multi option to True","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":51,"question":"To cleanly shut down MongoDB, what command should you use from the MongoDB shell?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"quit()","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"exit()","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"db.shutdownServer()","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"db.shutdown()","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":52,"question":"Given a customer collection which includes fields for gender and city, which aggregate pipeline shows the number of female customers in each city? (_Alternative_: How can you view the execution performance statistics for a query?)","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.members.aggregate([ {$match: {gender: \"Female\"}}, {$group: {_id: {city: \"$city\"}, number: {$sum: 1}}}, {$sort :{number: -1}}])`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`db.members.find({$match: {gender: \"Female\"}}, {$group: {_id: {city: \"$city\"}, number: {$sum: 1}}}.$sort ({number: -1})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.members.find([ {$match: {gender: \"Female\"}}, {$group: {_id: {city: \"$city\"}, number: {$sum: 1}}}, {$sort :{number: -1}}])`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.members.aggregate([ {$match: {gender: \"Female\"}}, {$sort :{number: -1}}])`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":53,"question":"When no parameters are passed to `explain()`, what mode does it run in?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"wireTiger mode","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"executionStats mode","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"queryPlanner mode","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"allPlansExecution mode","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":54,"question":"What is the correct query to find all of the people who have a home phone number defined?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.person.find({exists: 'homePhone'});`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.person.exists({homePhone: true});`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.person.find({homePhone: {$exists: true}});`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`db.person.has('homePhone');`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":55,"question":"Which file in the MongoDB directly holds the MongoDB daemon?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"mongodb","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"mongo-daemon","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"daemon","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"mongod","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":56,"question":"You have just secured your previously unsecured MongoDB server, but the server is still not requiring authentication. What is the best option?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Restart the `mongod` process.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Issue the `secure()` command.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Issue the `mongoimport` command.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Issue the `authenticate()` command.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":57,"question":"What is the most accurate statement regarding MongoDB and ad hoc queries?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"MongoDB does not allow ad hoc queries; all queries require an index.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Ad hoc queries are allowed only in the paid version.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Ad hoc queries are allowed only through the ad hoc command.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"MongoDB allows ad hoc queries.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":58,"question":"In MongoDB, what does a projection do?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"allows you to do a calculation on the results","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"allows you to run queries on the server","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"allows you to select which fields should be in the return data","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"allows you to format the results for a display","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":59,"question":"To remove a database and all of its records from MongoDB, what operator should you use?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`dropDatabase()`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`removeAll()`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`clear()`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`deleteDatabase()`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":60,"question":"What option can be passed to start the MongoDB shell without connecting to a database?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`-db=null`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`--shell-only`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`--free`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`-nodb`","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":61,"question":"How can you improve the appearance of the output JSON that contains the `_id`?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`Use db.collection.set({$_id:pretty})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Create a second index`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`Use db.collection.format(numeric)`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`Use $_id = value`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":62,"question":"What happens to a Replica set oplog if it runs out of memory?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`The oplog will be saved on one of the secondary servers.`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`The oplog is capped collection and can't run out of memory`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`The MongoDB instance will fail`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`The oplog will stop recording logging information`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":63,"question":"MongoDB ships with a variety of files. Which file runs the MongoDB shell?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"mongo","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"mongo-s","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"shell","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"mongo-shell","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":64,"question":"How can you view the execution performance statistics for a query?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.performance.members.aggregate([ {$match: {gender: \"Female\"}}, {$group: {_id:{city:\"$city\"}, number: {$sum: 1}}}, {$sort : {number: -1}}])`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.members.aggregate([ {$match: {gender: \"Female\"}}, {$group: {_id: {city: \"$city\"}, number:{$sum:1}}}, {$sort: {number:-1}}]).explain(\"executionStats\")`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`db.members.aggregate([ {$match: {gender: \"Female\"}}, {$group:{_id: {city: \"$city\"}, number: {$sum: 1}}}, {$sort: {number: -1}}]).explain()`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.members.aggregate([ {$match: {gender: \"\"\"Female\"\"\"}}, {$group: {_id: {city: \"\"\"$city\"\"\"}, number: {$sum:1}}}, {$sort: {number: -1}}]).number()`","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":65,"question":"From the MongoDB shell, how do you execute a JavaScript file named list.js?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"node 'list.js'","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"exec('list.js)","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"run('list.js)","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"load('list.js)","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":66,"question":"Which MongoDB shell query will sort the customer's collection by name descending?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"db.customers.sort({name: -1}.find({})","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"db.customers.sort({name: -1})","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"db.customers.find({}).sort({name: -1})","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"db.customers.find({}).sort({name: 1})","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":67,"question":"Suppose you are using the mongoimport command to import personnel data and there is a unique index on the email field. What happens when there are duplicate emails in the import?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"The import command aborts without importing any records.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The import command imports records upto but not including the record, and then aborts.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The import command doesn't import the bad document but does import the rest.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"The import command prompts you to correct the bad record.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":68,"question":"You have a collection with millions of documents. Each time you attempt to sort. MongoDB runs out of memory. What might help?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Use the purge operator before the sort.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Return the entire collection and sort on the client.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Pass the --more-memory option.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Create an index on the field you are sorting.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":69,"question":"You need to be able to quickly find a word in a text field. What should you do?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Create a text index on the field and do a $text Query.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Create an single field index in descending order, and do a query for the word.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Do a $text query.","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"Create a $regex on the fields, and do a $regex query.","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":70,"question":"Which field is always included in a projection unless specifically excluded?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"index","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Name","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`_id`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"row number","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":71,"question":"After installing MongoDB on your machine, what must you do before launching Mongo?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"Create a user account.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Register online.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Create a data directory.","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"Establish security credentials.","answer":true,"code":false}]},{"id":72,"question":"How does a --jsonArray file need to be structured?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"as a properly formatted JSON array","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"as YAML","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"as plain text","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"as a BSON object","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":73,"question":"From the MongoDB shell, how do you display all of a database's memory usage?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"db.size()","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"db.info()","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"db.memory()","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"db.stats()","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":74,"question":"How do you create a new MongoDB user?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"db.createUser({})","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"db.insert({user: 1})","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"db.customers.newUser({})","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"db.newUser({})","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":75,"question":"What is the internal data structure of a MongoDB document?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"JSON (JavaScript Object Notation)","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"BSON (Binary JSON)","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"ORM (object relational mode)","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"MBF (MongoDB binary format)","answer":false,"code":false}]},{"id":76,"question":"Which projection shows only the FirstName and lastName fields of a document in the customers collection?","code":"","reference":"","choices":[{"text":"`db.customers.find({}, {firstName: 1, lastName: 1})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.find({}, {_id:0, firstName: 1, lastName: 1})`","answer":true,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.find({_id: 0, year: 1, maek: 1, model: 1})`","answer":false,"code":false},{"text":"`db.customers.find({}).project({firstName: 1, lastName: 1})`","answer":false,"code":false}]}]